Basic information such as the printer ID number, installation date and time, country/region settings, etc. 
Usage history such as toner use information, the number of sheets printed, scanning frequency, and maintenance 
information, etc. Paper use information, printing environment/conditions, scan job setting, etc. Basic device
information such as the model name, OS version, language, and display setting information, etc. Version information 
and usage history of device driver and application software

Some of the above information may not be sent depending on your model and/or application software.The sent information 
may be delivered to Canon's affiliated companies.The Internet connection fee shall be borne by each customer.If your 
Canon product is shared for use, the above information recorded in the shared product will be sent. If you are to agree, 
please convey this fact to the users who share the product and obtain their agreement as well beforehand.
